James A. Baker III Papers, 1957-2011 (bulk 1972-1992): Finding Aid MC197
Public Policy Papers
- Series 6: Chief of Staff, 1978-1986; 38 boxes
  - Subseries 6A. Correspondence, 1978-1985; 16 boxes
    - Alphabetical Files, 1978-1985; 11 boxes
      - Eckles, Robert, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 44)
      - Eden, John W, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 45)
      - Edwards, Jack, 1981; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 46)
      - English, Richard, 1983; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 47)
      - Evans, Robert B, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 48)
      - Evans, Thomas, 1982; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 49)
      - E Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Fahrenkopf, Frank J. Jr, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Falwell, Jerry, undated; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Fatjo, Tom J, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Feldman, Trude, 1985; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Feldstein, Martin, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Feulner, Edwin J, 1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Fiedler, Bobbi, 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Field, H. James, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Fields, Jack, 1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Finger, Jerry E, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Fitch, John C, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Fitzgerald, William H. G, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Flawn, Peter T, 1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Ford, Gerald R, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Franklin, Barbara H, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Frazier, L. E, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Frelinghuysen, Peter, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Friedersdorf, Max L, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Friedham, Jerry W, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - F Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Gabor, Eva, 1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Garment, Leonard, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Garth, David L, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 24)
      - Garwood, W. St. John, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Garwood, William L, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Gavin, John, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 27)
      - Gerry, Robert L. and Judy, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 28)
      - Getz, H. Leland, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 29)
      - Gill, Michael Doud, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 30)
      - Gillcrist, Dan, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 31)
      - Gillies, H. Wayne, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 32)
      - Gingrich, Newt, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 33)
      - Goldwater, Barry, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 34)
      - Gonzales, Roy G, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 35)
      - Gooden, Oswald, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 36)
      - Goodling, Bill, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 37)
      - Goodman, I. Robert, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 38)
      - Goyette, James A, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 39)
      - Gradison, Bill, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 40)
      - Graham, Billy, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 41)
      - Graves, Clifford W, 1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 42)
      - Gray, Robert Keith, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 43)
      - Green, Alan, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 44)
      - Grizzard, James P, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 45)
      - G Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 46)
      - Hackett, Ray, 1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 47)
      - Hagedorn, Tom, 1982; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 48)
      - Haggar, Edward R, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 49)
      - Halbouty, Michel T, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 50)
      - Hamblet, Janice and Newman, 1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 51)
      - Hambleton, George B. E, 1984; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 52)
      - Hamby, Kevin, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 53)
      - Hamill, Claud B, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 54)
      - Hargrove, James W, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 45, Folder 55)
      - Harlow, Bryce N, 1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Harrell, Morris, 1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Harper, John C, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Harris, Paul, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Hartman, David, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Hasenkamp, Bruce H.,1981-1982, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Hatch, Orrin G, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Hatfield, Mark O, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Haw, Drane, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Haynes, William R, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Hecht, Chic, 1985; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Heckman, Robert C, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Hedges, Daniel K, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Heinz, John, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Helms, J. C, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Helms, Jesse, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Hempstone, Smith, 1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Henry, Audrey, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Hermes, Peter, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Herring, Joanne, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - Heston, Charlton, 1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - Heyer, George S. Jr, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Hicks, R. Miller, 1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Hidalgo, Edward, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Hill, A. Alan, 1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - Hillman, Elsie, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - Hodsoll, Frank, 1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Holt, Marjorie S, 1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 28)
      - Holton, Linwood, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 29)
      - Hooks, Benjamin L, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 30)
      - Hopkins, Porter, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 31)
      - Horton, Frank, 1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 32)
      - Howell, Paul, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 33)
      - Hudson, Edward J, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 34)
      - Hunter, Duncan, 1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 35)
      - Hutchison, Kay Bailey, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 36)
      - H Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 37)
      - Iacocca, Lee, 1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 38)
      - Ireland, Andy, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 39)
      - I Miscellaneous, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 40)
      - Jachym, John J, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 41)
      - Jackson, Jesse, 1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 42)
      - Jaworski, Leon, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 43)
      - Jepsen, Roger W, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 44)
      - Johnson, Thomas A. Jr, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 45)
      - Jones, Bob, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 46)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, 1980; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 47)
      - J Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 48)
      - Kamin, Jake, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 49)
      - Kampelman, Max M, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 50)
      - Karlin, David A, 1981; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 51)
      - Kasich, John R, undated; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 52)
      - Kasten, Robert W. Jr, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 53)
      - Katz, S. Stanley, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 54)
      - Keene, David A, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 46, Folder 55)
      - Kemp, Jack, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Kemp, Joanne, 1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Kempener, I. H. "Denny", 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Kennedy, Edward M, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Kennerly, David Hume, 1980; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Kessel, John H, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Khachigian, Kenneth L, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Kilberg, Bobbie Greene, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Kilpatrick, James, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Kincaid, Walter G, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - King, Allan C, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Kissinger, Henry, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Korologos, Tom, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - K Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - LaFontant, Jewel, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Lamphere, Gilbert H, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Langlie, Arthur Sheridan, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Lavin, Franklin L, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Lawson, Eugene K, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Laxalt, Paul, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Lehrman, Lewis E, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Lesher, Richard L, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Leslie, James H, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Lewis, Leslie C, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Lilly, Francis X, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Linowitz, Sol M, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 26)
      - Livingston, Bob, 1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 27)
      - Livingston, Dodie, 1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 28)
      - Loeffler, Tom, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 29)
      - Lofton, John, 1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 30)
      - Lollar, J. H, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 31)
      - Longstreth, Bevis, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Lott, Trent, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 33)
      - Love, Ben, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 34)
      - Lugar, Richard, 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 35)
      - Luther, Monroe M, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 36)
      - Lyles, J. K, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 37)
      - L Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 38)
      - Madden, Wales Jr, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 39)
      - Madison, Alfreda, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 40)
      - Mahoney, David J, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 41)
      - Marriott, J. Willard, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 42)
      - Martel, Miles, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 43)
      - Martin, David, 1985; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 44)
      - Martin, F. E, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 45)
      - Mashek, John W, 1981; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 46)
      - Mathias, Charles McC, 1984; 1 folder (Box 47, Folder 47)
      - Mattingly, Mack, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Maxwell, David O, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - May, Philip S, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - McColpin, Andrew K, 1980; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - McCormick, Sanford E, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - McClure, James A, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - McCullough, Andrew Dossett, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - McCurdy, Wells and Della, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - McDonald, Alonzo C, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - McFarlane, Robert "Bud", undated; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - McHenry, Adams, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - McHenry, Barnabas, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - McHenry, Jerry, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - McHenry, Sandra, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - McKinney, John, 1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - McLaughlin, Linda, 1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - McLean, Roger D, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - McLennan, Judy, 1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - McNamar, R. T, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Mead, Charles M, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Means, H. F, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Melady, Thomas Patrick, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Meyerhoff, Lyn, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Meyers, John H. and Alice, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Michel, Robert H, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 25)
      - Middendorf, J. William, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 26)
      - Miller, Johnathan, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 27)
      - Miller, Loye, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 28)
      - Miller, Mary Ellen, 1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 29)
      - Milliken, Roger, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 30)
      - Milliken, William G, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Minor, W. Ernst, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Minow, Newton N, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Mitchell, Andrea, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Mitler, Milton E, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Mizell, Wilmer D, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - Molinari, Guy V, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Moore, Kate L, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Moore, Preston, 1981-1984; 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 39-40)
      - Moore, Richard A, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - Moore, Roger Allan, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Moran, John J, 1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Morrison, Susan, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - Mosbacher, Robert, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Motley, Langhorne A, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Munn, James S, 1984; 1 folder (Box 48, Folder 47)
      - M Miscellaneous (MacGregor, Clark-Miller, Daniel), 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - M Miscellaneous (Miller, Jim-Myers, Keith), 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Nalen, Craig A, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Nelson, Jack, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Niemczyk, Julian N, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Nixon, Richard, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Nofziger, Lyn, 1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Nolan, Martin P, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Norris, Jan Douglas, 1978-1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Novak, Robert, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - N Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - O'Brien, George M, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - O'Brien, Hugh, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - O'Donnell, Patrick E, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - O'Donnell, Peter, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - O'Leary, Jeremiah, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - O'Neill, Thomas P. (Tip), 1980; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Orr, Verne, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Oxley, Michael G, 1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - O Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Palmer, Linda, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Parks, Fred, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Pashayan, Charles J, 1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Paton, David, 1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Pauken, Tom, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Pepper, Claude, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - Percy, Charles H, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Perlmutter, Nathan, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - Peterkin, George Jr, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Peterson, Elly M, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Peterson, Peter G, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Pflieger, John E, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Phillips, Howard, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Pickering, Charles, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - Pierce, Samuel R. Jr, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - Pillsbury, George S, 1981; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - Plante, William M, undated; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - Pollock, Howard W, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - Pratt, Lawrence, 1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - Pressler, Larry, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 49, Folder 40)
      - Price, Robert D, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Principal, Victoria, 1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Proxmire, William, 1982-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Putze, Louis, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - P Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Quaal, Ward L, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Quartel, D. R. Jr, 1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Quayle, Dan, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Q Miscellaneous, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Randall, Carolyn Dineen, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Randall, Hally Ballinger and Fairfax, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Ray, Robert D, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Reagan, Maureen, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Regan, Donald T, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Rendel, Betty, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Reynolds, Nancy Clark, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Rhatican, William F, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Rhodes, John J, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Ricardo-Campbell, Rita, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Richards, Richard, 1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Richardson, E, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Ridings, Dorothy S, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Riggs, Douglas A, 1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Robinson, Gilbert A, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Rodgers, Joe M, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Rosenbaum, Richard M, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Roth, Michael, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Roussel, Peter, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Rove, Karl, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Ruckelshaus, William D, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - Rudd, Eldon, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Runnells, Clive, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Ruppe, Loret Miller, 1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Rush, Stockton R, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Ruth, Thomas G, 1980; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - R Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 39)
      - Saint Martin's Episcopal Church Vestry, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 40)
      - Sammons, James H, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Sanchez, Rodolfo Balli, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 43)
      - Schmitt, Harrison, 1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Schmults, Edward C, 1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 45)
      - Schneider, Claudine, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 46)
      - Schroeder, Patricia, 1985; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 47)
      - Schuette, Bill, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 48)
      - Schulze, Richard T, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 49)
      - Scott, Ray, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 50)
      - Scowcroft, Brent, 1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Shepherd, Robert A. Jr, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Sherrerd, John J. F, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 53)
      - Shipley, Carl L, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 54)
      - Shultz, George P, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 55)
      - Siljander, Mark D, 1984; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 56)
      - Simpson, Alan K, 1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 57)
      - Simpson, John R, 1983; 1 folder (Box 50, Folder 58)
      - Sinnott, Barbara J, 1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Smith, Ashley, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Smith, William French, 1982-1985; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Snelling, Richard A, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Snowe, Olympia J, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Sorg, Walter Larke, 1980; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Sotirhos, Michael, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Sparks, David M, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Sparling, James M, 1980; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Specter, Arlen, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Spivey, Bruce E, 1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Stahl, Lesley, 1983; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Stanley, Ralph L, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Stella, Frank D, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Stevens, Ted, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Stimpson, William H, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Stockdale, James, 1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Stone, Marvin L, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Stone, Roger J, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Strake, George W. Jr, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Stroock, Tom, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Sutterborne, Charles, 1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Symington, James W, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - S Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Tao, Wesley, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Tartt, Blake, 1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Thomas, Cal, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Thomas, Lowell, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Thompson, James R, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Thompson, Robert E, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - Thompson, Robert J, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Thone, Charles, 1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Thornburgh, Dick, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Thornhill, Bill, 1983; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 34)
      - Thurmond, Strom, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 35)
      - Timberg, Bob, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 36)
      - Timmons, William E, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 37)
      - Touchstone, Gifford, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 38)
      - Tower, John G, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 39)
      - Towery, Roland Kenneth, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 40)
      - Treen, David C, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 41)
      - Trowbridge, Alexander B, 1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 42)
      - Tutwiler, Temple W. and Peggy, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 43)
      - T Miscellaneous, 1980-1985; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 44)
      - Unruh, Paula, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 45)
      - Upham, Chester R. Jr, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 46)
      - U Miscellaneous, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 47)
      - Valenti, Jack, 1981; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 48)
      - Van Praag, H. John, 1984; 1 folder (Box 51, Folder 49)
      - Vander Jagt, Guy, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Vander Myde, Paul, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Verstandig, Lee L, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Villegas, Oscar Diaz de, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Vinovich, Ralph, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Visser, Robert P, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Vogt, Carl W, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Voinovich, George V, 1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Von Damm, Helene, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - V Miscellaneous, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Walker, George H, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Walker, June Grace, 1981-1985; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Walker, Ronald H, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Walt, Lewis W, 1981; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Wanninski, Jude, 1981-1984; 1 folder (Box 52, Folder 15)